Waleed Salah

Frontend Developer

PERSONAL INFO

- Date of birth

 December 18th, 1993
- GenderMale
- Civil Status

 Married

CONTACT

- Sharqia-Egypt
- +201010806145
- B +201553438886
- eng.waleed.salah@outlook.com
- (m) waleed-salah-056a2816a
- github.com/DevWaleedS
- <u>devwaleeds.github.io/portfolio</u>

PROFILE

II'm a skilled frontend developer with over +3 years of experience creating user-focused digital solutions.

I specialize in developing professional dashboards and robust educational as well as e-commerce platforms.

With a strong command of technologies like ReactJS, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Material-UI, Tailwind CSS, Axois, JWT and Bootstrap, combined with my passion for continuous improvement.

Beyond my technical expertise,

I'm valuing effective communication and continuous learning.

My dedication to excellence and problem-solving mindset enables me to tackle complex challenges and deliver outstanding results.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Management and Information Sep system

n Sep 2016 -May 2019

Misr Higher Institute for commerce & computer

EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer

2022 - Present

FAZ for information technology

- build Platform Apps like (Admin, users dashboards, & Website)
- create blogs system for users.
- build e-commerce platform & set up payment gateways.
- Problem-Solving and Innovation

software engineer

2020 - 2022

I TECH Company

I has been part of a team responsible of designing, developing and implementing cutting-edge software solutions.

My role involved leveraging my technical expertise problem-solving skills, and collaborative approach to deliver high-quality software products.

Freelancer frontend developer

2020 - 2022

I'm Specializing in crafting captivating user interfaces and seamless user experiences. with a strong focus on clients, satisfaction and project excellence.

i offer my services to diverse clients and projects on the platform.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript, ES6+, OOP.
- React JS.
- React Router Dom
- Redux, Redux toolkit
- Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS
- Material UI, React Bootstrap
- React charts.
- Styled Components.
- Axios & Handle APIs.
- WebPack.
- JWT tokens & Login authentication.
- Figma & Adobe XD.
- Basic networks (OSI layers. DNS)
- Dealing with Backend & API Requests.
- Dealing with Postman App
- Git & Github.
- Project Management Tools.

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Problem-solving
- Time management
- Communication
- Adaptability
- Creativity
- Interpersonal skills
- Work ethic
- Attention to detail

LANGUAGES

- ARABIC (Native)
- English

PROJECTS

nueawin.com

Link: Demo

An association to serve people with disabilities and the elderly within the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.

eCommerce Template

link: Demo

A simple template for an e-commerce store using the latest front-end technologies. contain products, contact us, blogs, and shopping cart pages. you cant search products, filters products and more.

responsive-admin-dashboard

link: Demo

It is a simple dashboard compatible with all screens.

runawa

link: Demo

Ranwa Foundation Event supplies rental

bdaa

link: Demo

Ebdaa is one of the companies working in interior design and furniture manufacturing. The company is also a member of the Furniture Export Council. learn more

Build medical website

Link: Demo

this project created pay react and react router Dom, its contain many section and pages like services, blogs, login& register pages.

motors-city

Link: Demo

MotorsCity is the best, easiest and fastest way to buy a new or used car. We are working to make the car buying experience easier.

kareem protein healthydrink-landing

Link: Demo

A landing page for a healthy drink sold within the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia - supported in both Arabic and English